[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The metal cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the medium cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Bamboo"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Plastic"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium plastic cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the medium plastic cube lighter than the large concrete cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small metal cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large concrete cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small metal cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large concrete cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium plastic cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium plastic cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large bamboo cube travel to quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium plastic cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium plastic cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small metal cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large concrete cube and the large bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The large bamboo cube and the small metal cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the medium plastic cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube and the small metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small metal cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small metal cube and the large bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the large bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium plastic cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]